JOSE **FLORES**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER





(+593) 987 035 780

xfirepc.com contact@xfirepc.com

Ecuador (Quito)



₩ ABOUT ME

I'm a Web and mobile developer based in Ecuador. Over the past 7 years, I've worked with a diverse type projects from basic web desing to mobile apps and simple games, I love to create optimized and beautiful things. Knowledge is free and I love to learn.



MAIN SKILLS

PHP (Laravel, Symfony) JavaScript (React, Node.js) Python (Flesk, FastAPI)

Linux

Docker

HTML/CSS

SOL/NO SOL



SOFT SKILLS

Emotional Intelligence

Problem Solving

Communication

Teamwork and Collaboration



LANGUAGES

ENGLISH B1

SPANISH NATIVE

EDUCATION

UNIR - SPAIN

2020 - 2024

CINCO DE JUNIO

COMPUTER ENGINEERING DEGREE BACHELOR COMPUTER SCIENCE 2010 - 2016

COURSES - CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft - Azure Fundamentals AZ-900

Microsoft - Professional Fundamentals of Software Development

Platzi - Career JavaScript Development

Platzi - Career PHP Backend Development

JOB EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

2020 - 2024

BitMedia Technology / Ecuador

Development of ERP applications, mobile apps, management of controlled environments and cloud, APIs, and interactive interfaces.

FREELANCE

2015 - 2020

Worldwide

Custom web application development, logo and banner design, and online store creation.

PASANT 2014 - 3 mos

Ministry of Hydrocarbons / Ecuador

Help desk, computer equipment maintenance, inventory control, software installation

REFERENCES

FABRICIO ZAMBRANO

Gerente - SpiderNetwork Tel: +593 969 852 966

Email: fabricio@spidernetwork.com.ec

CARLOS YÁNEZ

Gerente - BitMedia Technology Tel: +593 995 077 401

Email: carlosy@bitmedia.technology